{
    "subject": "resource/Rolo_Tomassi",
    "predicate": "property/background",
    "object": "group_or_band",
    "human_readable": "The background of Rolo Tomassi is a group or band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9383553862571716,
            "question": "Is Rolo Tomassi a solo artist or a group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8089249134063721,
            "question": "Are there any prominent members of Rolo Tomassi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7568736672401428,
            "question": "When was Rolo Tomassi formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7168859243392944,
            "question": "What genre of music is Rolo Tomassi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6870735287666321,
            "question": "What is the overall style of Rolo Tomassi's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6824650764465332,
            "question": "Where is Rolo Tomassi from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6637405753135681,
            "question": "What instruments are commonly used by Rolo Tomassi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5343263745307922,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by Rolo Tomassi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45008787512779236,
            "question": "Has Rolo Tomassi released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3814244568347931,
            "question": "Has Rolo Tomassi won any awards or received recognition?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The background of Rolo Tomassi is a group or band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5571_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Rolo Tomassi released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5571_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular songs by Rolo Tomassi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5571_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments are commonly used by Rolo Tomassi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5571_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5571_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain:\n\n* All the provided text files describe Rolo Tomassi as a band or musical group.  Terms like \"band\", \"group\", and their description of releasing music (\"new record\", \"albums\") strongly support this classification. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the evaluation of whether the information supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all five documents mention Rolo Tomassi as a \"band\" from Sheffield, England. They also describe their musical style and performances, which suggests that they are indeed a group or band, rather than an individual author or person."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Rolo Tomassi being a British progressive metal band from Sheffield, which supports the statement that the background of Rolo Tomassi is that of a group or band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}